Michelle Brytowski

Full-Stack Web Developer (MERN)

Westminster, CO 80234 (970) 281-7417 mn.brytowski@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/michelle-brytows

ki

Profile: https://mbrytowski.github.io/FinalPortfolio/

GitHub: https://github.com/MBrytowski

SUMMARY

MERN (MongoDB, Express, React & Node) Full-Stack Developer with attention to detail, strong work ethic and time management skills. Experience in the field include six months in the Web Development Bootcamp through the University of Denver. This certification has provided the skills to hit the ground running in a web development role.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS (including frameworks Bootstrap and Foundation), Javascript, jQuery, Firebase, AJAX, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, PHP, React.js & Handlebars.js

PROJECTS

LIRI | Node.js, Javascript | Github

Back-End Developer

A Node-based app to search multiple APIs.

- Utilizes OMDB, Spotify and Bands-In-Town APIs.
- Node-based, no front-end design

FriendFinder | Node, Javascript | Github | Live

Full-Stack Developer

Web-based app to match the user to friends based their quiz score.

- Utilizes Bootstrap, CSS and Node for a dynamic UI/UX
- Tapped into Javascript to compare values for the new user and those in the database

Trail Headz | Javascript, Axios | Github | Live

Front-End Developer

App that takes user search input and finds hiking trails located near them.

- Learned Foundation (CSS Framework) and implemented into the project.
- Utilizes REI Hiking API, Google Geo Locations API and Colorado Hiking Subreddit API.

EXPERIENCE

FirstBank, Lakewood, CO - Commercial Loan Coordinator

JANUARY 2016 - PRESENT

- Entrusted to train new coordinators.
- Promoted to specialized Business Lending loans after six months.
- Completed an average of 10 loans per week for closing

FirstBank, Lakewood, CO - Credit Card Representative

MARCH 2014 - DECEMBER 2015

- Assisted branch and corporate personnel with Credit Card maintenance.
- Completed monthly and quarterly reporting and documents.

Starbucks, Louisville, CO - Barista

OCTOBER 2013 - MARCH 2014

- Prepared beverages and pastries to customer specifications.
- Supported management with other miscellaneous tasks throughout the store.

Centura Health, Louisville, CO - Radiologic Technologist

OCTOBER 2012 - OCTOBER 2013

- Experienced with GE imaging equipment and Fuji image processing.
- Assisted with clerical, reception and registration duties as needed.

Med Peds Clinic, Fort Collins, CO - Medical Receptionist

JULY 2011 - OCTOBER 2012

- Provided excellent customer service to patients.
- Input patient data into Meditech and Allscripts record systems

EDUCATION

University of Denver, Web Development Bootcamp, Denver, CO - Certificate

April 2019

MERN Full-Stack Training

North Dakota State University, Fargo, ND - Bachelor of Science

December 2010

B.S in Radiologic Science, minor in Chemistry